{
    "subject": "resource/Knowing_Me_Knowing_You_with_Alan_Partridge_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Rebecca_Front",
    "human_readable": "The TV series 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' stars Rebecca Front.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9787929654121399,
            "question": "Describe the character played by Rebecca Front in 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.963865339756012,
            "question": "Which actor appears alongside Rebecca Front in 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9476351141929626,
            "question": "Who stars in the TV series 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.838021457195282,
            "question": "Is 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' a popular show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7961910367012024,
            "question": "Name a TV show that Rebecca Front has been in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7916658520698547,
            "question": "What is the name of the TV series featuring Rebecca Front?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7452937960624695,
            "question": "What type of program is 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6663482189178467,
            "question": "When did 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5497502088546753,
            "question": "Is Rebecca Front known for comedic roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2799052596092224,
            "question": "What other projects has Rebecca Front been involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The TV series 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' stars Rebecca Front.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3277_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rebecca Front known for comedic roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3277_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3277_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of program is 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3277_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3277_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple, I will look for mentions of \"Rebecca Front\", \"TV series\", and \"'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'\".\n\nThe answer is:\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents mention Rebecca Front as a veteran comedy performer and writer on British television.\n* The documents also mention her appearances in the TV series \"The Thick of It\" (BBC Four/Two, 2005-2012), \"Big Train\", \"Up The Women\", and other shows.\n* Furthermore, the documents specifically mention that Rebecca Front starred in the TV series \"'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge'\".\n\nSo, according to the information provided, the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the television show \"Knowing Me, Knowing You with Alan Partridge\" and mention that Rebecca Front starred in it. Therefore, the statement \"The TV series 'Knowing Me Knowing You with Alan Partridge' stars Rebecca Front\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}